<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Apatha Wiki]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Apatha Wiki</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:12:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:12:17 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[0. Welcome]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Welcome to the one and only ApathaWiki! Hopefully this makes it easier to trawl through the absolute boatload of information I am about to dump on you. I will continue updating this wiki throughout the campaign.<br>For a summary of the important things you'll need to consider when creating your character, go to <a data-href="Character Creation Notes" href="/Character Creation Notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Character Creation Notes</a>.<br>Otherwise, here's some additional info for you to look through.<br><br>
<br><a data-href="Intro to Apathan Geography" href="/Intro to Apathan Geography.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Intro to Apathan Geography</a>
<br><a data-href="Intro to Apathan Cosmology" href="/Intro to Apathan Cosmology.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Intro to Apathan Cosmology</a>
<br><a data-href="Intro to Apathan Religion" href="/Intro to Apathan Religion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Intro to Apathan Religion</a>
<br><a data-href="Politics of Apatha" href="/Politics of Apatha.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Politics of Apatha</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Maps of Apatha" data-href="Maps of Apatha" href="/Maps of Apatha.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">List of Maps</a>
<br><a data-href="Apathan Languages" href="/Apathan Languages.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Apathan Languages</a>
<br><a data-href="List of Countries" href="/List of Countries.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">List of Countries</a>
<br><a data-href="List of Religions" href="/List of Religions.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">List of Religions</a>
<br><br><br>In terms of content expect stuff that is large in scale - it won't necessarily be driven by war, but war will play a large part. Heavily social - a minor amount of adventuring and exploring.]]></description><link>0. Welcome.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0. Welcome.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alta]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Alta is one of Apatha's moons. It is the smaller of the two, and orbits at a closer distance - one cycle takes around 23 days. It emits a dim red light.]]></description><link>Alta.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Alta.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:58:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apathan Languages]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Refer to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://i.imgur.com/1BvEhNr.jpg" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://i.imgur.com/1BvEhNr.jpg" target="_blank">this map</a> for the regions in which specific languages are spoken. <br>Apatha does not use the standard common languages. Instead, there are 13 language families, with their main languages listed as subheadings (this is an incomplete list; more languages will be added later). All languages under a language family are mutually intelligible. Creatures of different races from the same region will speak dialects of that region's language.<br>When creating your character, replace Common with the language family that is spoken in the region you are from. If given more languages, you may pick whatever language families you wish from the list below, including the Exotic languages and Pan-Apathan. I would HIGHLY suggest Pan-Apathan.<br><br>
<br>Slavaric (Russian)

<br>Slavarian


<br>Qianian (Chinese)

<br>Qianese


<br>Youraic (Japanese)

<br>Youraian


<br>Nioric (Xhosa)

<br>Nioran


<br>Dvalic (Greek)

<br>Telysian


<br>Süden (German)
<br>Madhyic (Hindi)
<br>Bangkan (Bahasa Indonesia)

<br>Bangka


<br>Qalfic (Ancient Egyptian)
<br>Emeritic (Latin)

<br>Emeritan


<br>Aviegnic (French)

<br>Aviegnian
<br>Fasilican
<br>Amathrian


<br>Desert-Tongue (Arabic)
<br>Shaasan (Mix of Central Asian)
<br>Lajasan (Portuguese)
<br>In addition to these languages, there is Pan-Apathan, a sort of lingua franca for the entire planet that occupies a similar space to Latin on Earth.<br>The Exotic DND languages still exist:<br>
<br>Draconic
<br>Sylvan
<br>Undercommon
<br>Celestial
<br>Deep Speech
<br>Infernal
<br>Primordial
]]></description><link>Apathan Languages.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Apathan Languages.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Azim]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Azim is one of Apatha's moons. It is further out than Alta - one orbital cycle takes 40 days - it is also brighter and larger than <a data-href="Alta" href="/Alta.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Alta</a>, reflecting a bright white light.<br>Every 72 cycles, Azim disappears completely from the sky for exactly 40 days. When it returns it swells to 3 times its diameter and emits a bright blue light. The next night is a regular full moon of normal size.]]></description><link>Azim.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Azim.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Character Creation Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>In addition to your character and background, you also have the option of creating the nation your character comes from. You are free to pick any one of the currently existing nations or carve out a new nation of your own choice. Feel free to make your character an important character in that nation’s politics!<br>If you want to create your own nation, expect to work very closely with me to iron out the specific details of that nation's politics, history, culture, etc.<br><br>When creating your character, replace Common with the language family that is spoken in the region you are from according to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://i.imgur.com/C096q2j.jpg" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://i.imgur.com/C096q2j.jpg" target="_blank">this map</a>. If any feature gives you more languages, you may pick whatever language families you wish from the list given in <a data-href="Apathan Languages" href="/Apathan Languages.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Apathan Languages</a>, including the Exotic languages and Pan-Apathan. <br>I would HIGHLY suggest taking Pan-Apathan as it may well be the only common language within the party.<br>If you want your character/country to have a super specific language, that specific language will be categorized under the corresponding language family.<br><br>I’ve asked you all to not make your characters direct anime references.* But, if a character in your backstory is explicitly anime or manga-related they will have some relation to the Church of Madoka. Read more in <a data-href="Intro to Apathan Religion" href="/Intro to Apathan Religion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Intro to Apathan Religion</a>.<br>*I should clarify that when I say 'no direct anime references' I mean straight up playing an anime character without changes to their backstory, etc. This was because the Saints of the Church of Madoka are all real anime characters. Being inspired by anime is perfectly ok.<br><br>The campaign will start in the small seaside town of Mizuma, in the south of Yourai, but don’t feel like that necessarily restricts you to playing a nomad. We can always figure out a way for you to get here. Mizuma is indicated on <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://i.imgur.com/gisbb3w.png" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://i.imgur.com/gisbb3w.png" target="_blank">this map</a>.]]></description><link>Character Creation Notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character Creation Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Church of Madoka]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Church of Madoka is a religion on Apatha that worships the god Madoka, and a large array of other smaller saints. All of these saints are anime characters. Some commonly known saints include Naruto the Loyal, Honoka the Sedulous, and Light the Brilliant.<br>The Saints are all characters from popular stories. The Church's canon is continuously expanded to include a greater number of saints as different stories increase in popularity.<br><br>Followers of Madokanism read works made by its members, and through discussion of the material strengthen their own creative abilities. Members are not expected to do art, but instead to see the creativity and ingenuity at work in their everyday lives.<br>The two core concepts at the heart of Madokanism are Inspiration and Obsession. The Church teaches its followers to strive for the former and reject the latter.<br>
<br>Inspiration is the concept that humans can build on top of each other, creating things that become increasingly beautiful.
<br>Obsession is an overly unhealthy preoccupation with the art of others.
<br>The Church believes that art is powerful, in both positive and negative ways. Art is powerful, but can be wielded in positive and negative ways; to be a good follower of Madoka, one must learn to appreciate the beauty in art and the hard work put into creating it, and allow it to inspire them to create their own. However, it is important to not let one's love for any specific piece of art consume them, turning them into someone who obsesses over it but does nothing with that obsession.<br>'Art' is a nebulous term in scripture; it refers to anything related to creative endeavors. For example, scientific inquiry is a form of art. The Church differentiates the 'Pure Arts' (Visual Art, Sculpture, Narrative, Dance) from the 'Analytical Arts' (Sciences, Humanities) and 'Practical Arts' (Farming, Smithing, Weaving).<br><br><br>Madokanism's core text, which isn't usually read very often, is the Tale of Madoka, a short book that essentially summarizes the events of //Puella Magi Madoka Magica// (excluding Rebellion). The text heavily emphasizes the ingenuity that Madoka showed with her wish, which effectively allowed her to end the cycle of suffering and which led to happiness for all.<br>The different Churches have different ways of adding to their canon, although Churches in close proximity to one another will canonize each others' saints as long as they believe the stories line up with their particular church's ideals.<br>Madoka is characterized as a god of Creation, with all followers seeking to emulate her example through creations of their own.<br><br>Orthodox Madokanism is a religion of the people in <a data-href="Slavaria" href="/Slavaria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Slavaria</a>. The Church largely served as a unifying force in the Slavarian plains before the advent of the empire, so it dominates government.<br>The orthodox church publishes <a data-href="Madokan Monthly" href="/Madokan Monthly.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Madokan Monthly</a>, a monthly manga and written fiction anthology.<br>The Church of Madoka heavily sponsors art of pretty much every kind, including anti-government art. This has had the effect of making government more transparent and accountable - at least within the heartlands. While the Church permits art criticizing the government's actions in its colonies, the public's perception of these lands is generally quite poor and both Church and Government make a point not to spread this information.<br>At the same time, the Madokan Church has been incorporated into government as one of its core branches.<br><br><br>The Church of Madoka is about as popular as the native religion, <a data-href="Jindo" href="/Jindo.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Jindo</a>. The Emperor of Yourai participates in rituals from both to legitimize his rule among the population.<br>Youraian Madokanism is significantly more restrictive than in <a data-href="Slavaria" href="/Slavaria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Slavaria</a> - it represses political art and is the religion of the upper and upper middle classes.]]></description><link>Church of Madoka.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Church of Madoka.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ethereal Plane]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The plane that surrounds the Material Plane, Feywild and Shadowfell. The ethereal plane looks like a dark forest that occasionally turns into craggy peaks.]]></description><link>Ethereal Plane.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Ethereal Plane.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:58:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intro to Apathan Cosmology]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Apatha has two small moons, <a data-href="Azim" href="/Azim.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Azim</a> and <a data-href="Alta" href="/Alta.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Alta</a>. It is the fourth planet from its star, Isatala. In order, the planets go:<br>Isatala → Isaia → Dawad → Thalon → Apatha<br>Apathans look to the night sky and see murky darkness - there are no stars.<br>In terms of the Great Wheel cosmology, the Material Plane exists, with Shadowfell and the Feywild overlapping it, and all three are surrounded by the <a data-href="Ethereal Plane" href="/Ethereal Plane.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ethereal Plane</a>, then Astral Plane. Anything beyond this will be of minimal importance to the campaign.]]></description><link>Intro to Apathan Cosmology.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Intro to Apathan Cosmology.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intro to Apathan Geography]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The inhabitants of the planet Apatha are no stranger to earthquakes - the earth shudders and cracks incessantly no matter where on the planet you are, increasing in intensity as you get nearer to the web of mountains that crisscross the planet’s surface.<br>Apathan mountains can reach heights of up to 20 km, much higher than on Earth.<br>There are three major continents on Apatha:<br>
<br>Estra is the westernmost continent on the map, and location where the campaign will begin. It is split cleanly into North and South by The Spine, a mountain range that stretches from the far north in Slavaria to the western coasts of Niora in the south.
<br>Welde is the largest continent and slightly behind Estra in development.
<br>Terra Nova was discovered separately by multiple nations within the last 100 years, all of whom have set up colonies on the continent.
]]></description><link>Intro to Apathan Geography.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Intro to Apathan Geography.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intro to Apathan Religion]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Gods exist on Apatha, but Clerics do not call upon their power directly.<br>The most prominent religion on Apatha is the <a data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Church of Madoka</a>, a religion that has spread pretty much all over the world and has branches almost everywhere. They worship the great god Madoka. Their doctrines value creation and ingenuity from the individual - many of its followers pursue creative outlets.]]></description><link>Intro to Apathan Religion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Intro to Apathan Religion.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:46:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jindo]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Jindo is a religion native to <a data-href="Yourai" href="/Yourai.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Yourai</a>.<br>Jindo is inseparable from the myth of the first Emperor Jinshō, who is said to have conquered the core territories after being granted the powers of Umashi-kami, the God of Power. The Emperor soon realized that Umashi-kami planned to rule the world through him, manipulating him like a puppet to his own ends. Emperor Jinshō rejected this, swore off the god's power, and finished the job without divine aid.<br>Jindo quite literally means 'the path of men'. Doctrines focus on the power of the self, honed through rigorous application of oneself to a particular practice. Followers of Jindo worship Emperor Jinshō, and through studying his example they learn of their own personal power. Practitioners from different sects hone their power in different ways: for instance martial arts, creative expression, or meditation.]]></description><link>Jindo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Jindo.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[List of Countries]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Refer to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://i.imgur.com/guxO1NJ.jpg" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://i.imgur.com/guxO1NJ.jpg" target="_blank">this map</a> to see exactly where these nations are. Some nations will have links - they contain more detailed info on said nation.<br>]]></description><link>List of Countries.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">List of Countries.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:54:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[List of Religions]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br><a data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Church of Madoka</a>
<br><a data-href="Jindo" href="/Jindo.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Jindo</a>
]]></description><link>List of Religions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">List of Religions.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:55:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Madokan Monthly]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Madokan Monthly is a monthly manga and literature publication released by the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Church of Madoka" data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Orthodox Church</a>. It is a thick tome, consisting of hundreds of different stories by a variety of authors. Followers are not expected to read everything in it - but they are expected to follow some of these stories as sources of ‘inspiration’.<br>Once in a while, the magazine runs reruns of classic stories by a new author. These classics, which are over a thousand years old, include:<br>
<br>The Tale of Madoka
<br>One Piece
<br>Naruto
<br>Maquia
<br>Anohana
<br>My Hero Academia
<br>Weebs and Wanderers
]]></description><link>Madokan Monthly.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Madokan Monthly.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Madokan Theology]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Although there are many regional variants of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Church of Madoka" data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Madokanism</a>, they all share a few common traits that group them together under the umbrella religion of ‘Madokanism’:<br>
<br>They all believe in a single god, Madoka, and believe that she moulded the world while defending it against the Kyubeys.
<br>They all believe in the primacy of art, and the importance of a balance between Inspiration and Obsession.
<br>They all believe that post-Canonization, the object or person being Canonized will become corporeal, having form and joining Madoka’s side in Heaven.
<br>That being said, there is a great deal of debate, both within individual branches and between branches:<br><br>When a character is Canonized into the Madokan Pantheon, is it merely a representation of Madoka’s approval of this character after they have already been made corporeal, or does the priest that carries out the Canonization channel Madoka’s power directly?<br>
<br>This has implications regarding the role of priests - whether they are merely messengers of Madoka or if they are true channelers of her power - and thus how they should be treated within the religion itself.
<br>This also has implications regarding how the Canonization process should be carried out, since the process used has certain implications regarding the interpretation of Madoka’s will.
<br><br>This is an extremely contentious issue within the Church. Some degree of focus is required for an individual to be able to analyse and parse art, but too much will be unhealthy. To decide on a boundary, some advocate personal responsibility: through stringent self-reflection, one can decide for themselves. Others advocate stringent rules: ie. limiting the amount of time people have to analyse works.<br>
<br>This has huge implications regarding what Madoka’s will truly is, and what she wanted her disciples to accomplish during their time living on Apatha.
<br><br>These are probably the most important issues in Madokan bureaucracy. They essentially ask the question of whether the religion should prioritise certain types of art over others:<br>
<br>The Question of Narrative Primacy: Many priests argue that because the core text of Madokanism, The Tale of Madoka, is a narrative piece, that the religion should prioritise narrative-based art forms over others.

<br>This interfaces with the Saint Personhood Issue as well.


<br>The Question of Purity: In an extension of the previous argument, some priests believe that the Pure Arts (ie. the Creative Arts - dance, music, narrative) should be prioritised over the Lower Arts (Analytical Arts - science, humanities; Practical Arts - farming, smithing).
<br><br>This issue revolves around the question of what kinds of art should deserve Canonization, and how that would work. Some priests argue that the concept of a Saint should be tied to the concept of personhood - ie. it should only be possible to Canonize a Saint if they can be conceptualised as people. Others believe that this is a narrow-minded way of thinking, and that Madoka sees all art as equally beautiful and valid.<br>
<br>This divide generally is prevalent between churches - for instance, the Orthodox Church is very much on the side of personhood; they will only ever Canonize saints that are characters in a narrative. On the other hand, some branches of Madokanism in the Emeritan Empire will regularly Canonize dance, music, sculpture, and other forms of art. They will even Canonize entire narratives as single Saints.
<br>However, for those who choose to open up Canonization to all art forms, there is the Question of Rites: how should people celebrate saints?
<br><br>This is a theological issue revolving around the nature of the stories that are Canonized. Specifically, what is the relation between fiction and reality? At its most practical, priests debate over whether the stories that Canonized characters come from are automatically also deemed to have truly happened and thus treated as some form of history. At its most philosophical, priests debate the very nature of reality - if we are all simply living within Madoka’s dream and all realities are equally true, even those we fabricate. Perhaps Madoka simply acknowledges our power because we are able to give a face to some of these realities that already exist.<br>
<br>This has massive implications for the Canonization Issue: if stories already exist, what is the true nature of Canonization itself?
]]></description><link>Madokan Theology.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Madokan Theology.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:05:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maps of Apatha]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>Maps of Apatha.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Maps of Apatha.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Politics of Apatha]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>There are currently four major political players on Apatha: Emerita, with a culture similar to the Roman Empire; Aviegne, with a culture similar to the French Empire; Niora, with a culture that is broadly sub-saharan African; and Slavaria, which has a culture similar to the Russian Empire.<br>Five years ago Slavarian and Aviegnian expansion increased in ferocity and brutality. Niora and Emerita soon followed suit. Rumors and stories of soldiers from all four nations wielding advanced weapons far beyond their time, wreathed in darkness, have spread among civilians.<br>Currently, Aviegne and Emerita are warring over the various colonies that they have established. Slavaria and Niora are still expanding on Estra and have not had any significant conflicts yet. That being said, most of the world is preparing for war with one of these empires.<br>Armies from the four empires are highly trained and very large, so they heavily rely on people with a D&amp;D ‘class’. Most soldiers go through some kind of combat training in military academies for their specific class. Armies usually feature a great number of Fighters, Rogues, Paladins, Clerics, Bards and Wizards. But smaller squadrons of other classes do exist.]]></description><link>Politics of Apatha.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Politics of Apatha.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:56:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Slavaria]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Slavaria's historical homeland lies in the large fertile plain between The Spine and the Frostpeaks. Historically it has been mostly agrarian, with bitter winters and warm summers. Most of the population is centered in the southern portion of these plains, around the four rivers just north of what is now Wei (albeit separated by a mountain range).<br><br>Slavaria is ruled by Dwarven Tsar, Miron IV, who is entering his 30th year of rule. He is currently focusing on conquering the kingdoms of Liu and Yourai.<br>The Church of Madoka forms one of the core branches of the Slavarian government, with a big hold on the general population. State and religion have had close ties in the Empire for centuries and the Church has a large impact on government.<br>The Slavarian government is one of the most welcoming in the world to art and invention. The heartland is one of the most vibrant cultural regions in the world, and the government is generally quite open and welcoming of new ideas.<br>This openness contrasts heavily with Slavaria's colonial possessions, which it treats with a cruelty that most Slavarians like to willfully ignore. A thriving slave trade exists, with routes taking slaves through the inland basins and onwards to Terra Nova.<br><br>Slavaria was the place where the <a data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Church of Madoka</a> originated, although since its founding in around the year 4100 it has long since spread worldwide. The vast majority of Slavarians still follow this religion.<br>The Orthodox Church, based in Slavaria, heavily sponsors art of pretty much every kind, including anti-government art. This has had the effect of making government more transparent and accountable - at least within the heartlands.]]></description><link>Slavaria.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Slavaria.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yourai]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Yourai has a history of over 3,000 years. The nation is rapidly urbanizing, with most cities (including the capital) situated along the Hara River and the coast.<br>Youraians see their empire as consisting of the core territories (which are bordered by the Spine, the Sokoku Mountains, and the coast of Estra) and the hinterlands (everywhere else).<br><br>Yourai is ruled by an Elven Emperor, Ryosuke Hamakichi, who has overseen a period of modernization and conquest. Under his rule Yourai emerged from feudal society and conquered its hinterlands.<br>Yourai is an open society, with its caste system abolished and most traces of feudal and manorial society gone from the nation. The Emperor participates in rituals from both dominant religions - <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Church of Madoka" data-href="Church of Madoka" href="/Church of Madoka.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Madokanism</a> and <a data-href="Jindo" href="/Jindo.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Jindo</a> - to legitimize his rule among the population.<br>There is a lot of tension between the two religions and they have a long history of bad blood.<br><br><br>The Church of Madoka is about as popular as Jindo, the native religion. The Emperor participates in rituals from both to legitimize his rule among the population.<br>]]></description><link>Yourai.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Yourai.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>